Oh,man!
天哪
-What's that? -Treeger's snaking the shower drain.
谁啊？ 崔格在通排水管
What in the name of hell?
这是什么东西？
Maybe he found your flip-flop.
可能是你的夹脚拖鞋
Is this porn?
这是A片吗？
I must have hit something on the remote.
我一定是按到什么了
Do we pay for this?
我们有付钱吗？
We didn't even pay our cable bill.
我们连第四台都没给钱
Maybe this is how they punish us.
也许这是处罚方式
Maybe we shouldn't pay our phone bill. Free phone sex.
也许我们应该欠电话费 免费色情电话
Maybe we shouldn't pay our gas bill.
也许我们应该欠瓦斯费
Hey,that lady's all kinds of naked.
那位小姐没穿衣服喔
Joey pressed something on the remote and it just came on.
乔伊不知道按了什么 它就冒出来了
It happened to me once. It was like finding money.
我有一次也按到过 跟检到钱一样爽
Finding money with naked people on it!
印有春宫图的钱
But I made the mistake of turning off the TV.
但后来我把电视关掉
I never got it back again.
就再也找不到了
And I'm sad.
我好伤心
Why would he turn off the TV?
他干嘛关电视？
The One with the Free Porn
本集播出：“为爱走天涯”
rainystar压制iPod-Mp4
Do we really have to watch this while we eat?
吃饭一定要看这个吗？
We don't know what could make this go away.
我们不知道它怎样会消失
So no one touches the remote, and no one touches the TV.
所以不准碰遥控器 也不准碰电视
And no one touches the air around the TV.
连电视周围的空气都不能扰动
Imagine a protective porn bubble, if you will.
就像有一个A片保护罩
I'm at least going to mute it.
起码也要静音 不要…
We still have porn.
A片还在
What are you doing? That's too heavy. Give it here.
你干什么？那个很重耶，给我
Oh,God.
天哪
好了
I'm too pregnant for lugging around a stupid massage table.
我实在不能再扛着按摩桌跑了
I need a job with a smaller table.
我得找个桌子小一点的工作
Or a job without a table.
或是不需要桌子的工作
You mean,like a doctor?
像医生吗？
You're blocking the porn!
菲比，你挡到A片了啦
That reminds me. I have to see my ob-gyn today.
这让我想到今天要做产检
Emily just went to the airport.
艾蜜莉去机场了
Why didn't you take her?
你怎么不送她去？
Her uncle had planned to do it.
她舅舅本来就打算送她
We said our goodbyes this morning.
我们今天早上道别了
You must feel horrible. Hey,the guys have free porn.
你一定很难受 隔壁有免费的A片
Hey,cheer up. You'll see her again,right?
高兴一点，你们会再见面吧？
I don't know.
我就是不知道
When I brought it up,she said...
我每次提起她就说
..."This is so fantastic. Why talk about the future?
“这样就很棒了” “何必谈到未来？”
-Let's enjoy" -Don't do the accent. It really bums me out.
“我们就…” 别学英国腔，我很受不了
Emily said I was pretty good.
艾蜜莉说我学得很好
Well,that's someone you should hang on to.
那你可得把握她
You've got to see her again.
你非再见她不可
-Why do you care? -Because!
你干嘛在意？ 因为...
You could live out my fantasy.
你可以实现我的幻想
You had fantasies about Emily?
你对艾蜜莉有幻想？
You know,the fantasy.
不是，就是那个幻想嘛
Meet a foreigner,fall madly in love and spend your lives together.
认识异乡人 疯狂坠入爱河，共度一生
Is that why you hung out with that Ukrainian kid in school?
所以你国中时 老跟那个乌克兰男生混？
Yeah,plus his mom used to put sour cream on everything.
对 另外他妈妈煮菜都会加酸奶油
Do you love her?
你爱她吗？
We said it would only be two weeks.
我们说好只在一起2星期
You love her.
你爱她
What is love,really?
什么是爱？
I knew you loved her!
我就知道你爱她
You go to the airport and tell her.
你得去机场告诉她
You'll probably catch her at the gate.
你应该会在登机门追上她
You'll call her name and yell "l love you!"
你会叫她的名字大喊 “我爱你”
She'll say "l love you too!"
她会说“我也爱你”
Then you will have the most amazing kiss.
然后你们会有最深情的一吻
Everyone at the gate will applaud.
登机门前掌声如雷
I am a good kisser.
我是很会接吻
Then you two can sneak into the cockpit.
然后你们可以溜进驾驶舱
Things will start to heat up.
气氛开始变得火热
And then a stewardess comes in....
然后一个空姐进来…
I've been watching too much porn.
我看太多A片了
-ls that the heartbeat? -That's it.
那是心跳吗？ 没错
Oh,my God!
天哪
This is so cool!
太酷了
Have we talked about multiple births?
我们谈过多胞胎的可能吗？
Let's take care of this one. If l get pregnant again,I have your card.
先搞定这一胎 要是再怀孕，我有你的名片
No,I'm getting three separate heartbeats.
不是，我听到三个心跳音
You guys were worried I wouldn't even have one.
三个？你们还担心我怀不成
Doctors are wrong all the time.
医生经常犯错
Are you sure that there are three?
你确定有三个？
-Definitely. -Oh,my God.
绝对的 天哪…天哪！
So in a few months,I'll have three babies walking around inside me?
再过几个月 我体内会有三个宝宝逛大街？
It'll be like one of those log rides when they come shooting out.
他们出生时会跟连发炮一样
Giving birth to three is like giving birth to one.
其实生三个跟生一个一样
What do you know?
你懂什么？
-Have you ever had triplets? -No. I'm sorry,I haven't.
你生过多胞胎吗？ 抱歉，我没有
I'm going to use this a lot.
我应该多利用这句话
菲比
How'd it go at the doctor's?
产检结果怎样？
You know how,when you're walking down the street...
当你走在街上
...and you see three people in a row.
看到三个人走成一列
And you say "Oh,that's nice."
你不是会说“真好”？
没错 好
Good news! You'll have three babies.
好消息，你们有三个宝宝
Three babies?
三个宝宝？
I've finally got my band!
我总算可以组团了
We'll have a big family! I always wanted a big family.
我们会是个大家庭 我一直想要大家庭
Oh,God,I'm so glad you're happy! I was afraid you'd be freaked.
你们高兴就好 我还怕你们会捉狂
Why would we be freaked?
为什么要捉狂？
Because it's harder to raise them and the added expense.
因为三个养起来更累也更花钱
Right.
也对
No,back to happy. Back to happy!
不，继续高兴，继续高兴
It's going to be fine...
不，没问题的
...because I teach home ec.
因为… 我教家政
I can have 30 kids making baby clothes all year long.
我可以叫卅个学生 1整年都做婴儿服
It'll be like my very own little sweatshop.
就像我专属的廉价童工厂
I was thinking,ever since you said we'd have triplets.
自从你说是三胞胎，我就在想
The best thing for me to do is drop out of college and get a job.
我最好休学去找一份工作
No,you can't quit college.
不，法兰克 你不能放弃学业
You're in college?
你在念书？
Refrigerator college.
冷冻库专校
When we found out we were having a baby...
当我们发现有了孩子
...I figured I should have a career,you know?
我想说我应该有份事业
And I love refrigerators.
而且我很喜欢冷冻库
You can't give up on your dream!
你不能放弃你的梦想
No,it's okay. We're going to have three kids.
没关系，我们将有三个孩子
And that's a different kind of dream.
那是个不一样的梦
Three kids and no money.
三个孩子，一贫如洗
This is the boarding call for flight 009.
搭乘009班机的旅客请登机
艾蜜莉
What are you doing here?
天哪，你怎么来了？
I had to see you before you took off.
我得在你走之前再见你一面
You are so sweet.
你真好
That's a big candy bar.
好大的三角巧克力
I had the most amazing time with you.
我跟你在一起过得好开心
Me too.
我也是
This is the final boarding call for flight 009.
009班机起飞前最后广播
Well,that's me.
那是我的班机
Here,have this.
给你
I'm only allowed one piece of carry-on.
只能有一件登机行李
等一下
Listen,I have to tell you something.
我有事要告诉你
I've been thinking.
我一直在想…
I'm just going to say it,okay?
我就直说了
I think...
我觉得…
...I love you.
...我爱你
Thank you.
谢谢
It's no problem.
不客气
What is that song?
这到底是什么歌？
It's the theme from Good Will Humping.
“蜜桃捕手”的主题曲
You know who doesn't like dirty movies? My boyfriend Joshua.
你们知道有谁不喜欢A片？ 我的新男朋友约书亚
Yeah,right.
是啊
He said he prefers to leave certain things to the imagination.
他说他喜欢保留一点想像空间
Did he also say that the dialogue was corny?
他有没有说那些对白很低俗
-And that he found it funny,not sexy? -Yes.
他觉得是可笑，不是性感？ 没错
Yeah,he likes porn.
他喜欢A片
Where you going?
你去哪里？
To find out if he really thinks models are too skinny.
去看他是不是真的觉得 超级名模都太瘦
How'd it go?
他们反应如何？
Frank has to quit college...
法兰克得休学
...because his super-fertile sister's having three babies.
因为很能生的姐姐一次怀三胎
I need to make money fast. I wanted to talk to you about an idea.
我得赚快钱 我想跟你谈一个想法
You work for a big company.
因为你在大公司上班
Insider trading.
内线交易
What information can you give me?
你有什么内幕可以给我？
They don't talk to us about that stuff.
大头不会跟我们讲这些
But I can get you free White-Out.
但我可以帮你A立可白
-Did you do what I said? -I did.
你有照我说的告诉她吗？ 有
-What'd she say? -"Thank you."
她怎么说？ “谢谢”
You're totally welcome. What'd she say?
不客气，她说什么？
She said,"Thank you."
她说“谢谢”
I said,"l love you."
我说“我爱你”
And she said,"Thank you."
她说“谢谢”
That's not right.
不对啊
Did you say you love her?
你说你爱她？
What were you trying to get her to do?
你想骗她做什么？
-What do I do now? -You play hard-to-get.
现在怎么办？ 你假装很难钓
She already lives in London.
她已经住在伦敦了
So you go to Tokyo.
你搬去东京
Forget it.
别想了
You told her you love her. It's over.
你说你爱她，没戏唱了
It is not over! You're over!
谁说的，你才没戏唱
What?
什么？
You know.
你懂我的意思
Good one.
好…说得好
It's not over. She'll call and tell you she loves you.
事情还没完 她会打来说她爱你
Her feelings were so strong that it scared her.
她的感觉强烈到令她害怕
Go home and wait for her call. She could call from the plane.
快回去等电话 她可能会从飞机上打
But if she doesn't call, it is definitely over!
要是她没打来， 那就是结束了
Unless,eventually,I call her to see what's going on...
除非最后我打给她探探口风
...and she says she'll call me back, but then she doesn't.
她说她会再打给我， 结果没打
Then it's over!
那就真的结束了
Way to be strong!
真够力
Can we watch cartoons on your TV?
我们可以在这里看卡通吗？
We need a porn break.
我们需要休息一下
We spent two hours watching In and Out and In Again.
我们看了2小时的 “杀进杀出又杀进”
Why don't you turn it off?
为什么不关掉算了？
Then we'd be the guys who turned off free porn.
那我们会变成关掉A片的白痴
Yeah,but that's not what you'd go by.
别人又不会那样叫你们
Look,I'm going to have a kid someday. Okay?
瑞秋，将来我会有小孩
And someday that kid is going to ask me if I ever turned off free porn.
他会问我有没有关掉免费A片
I don't wanna have to tell him that I did.
我不想说我有
Did you ever asked you dad that?
你有问过你爸吗？
I don't want to talk about it.
我拒谈这件事
Good,you're here!
太好了，你们都在
What you got there?
你手上拿什么？
This? I'm glad you asked.
这个？问得好
Don't you hate to cut a tin can with an ordinary steak knife?
用普通刀子切锡罐 不是很难切吗？
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你们在想什么
Pregnant woman slays four?
“孕妇发狂砍杀四人”？
-Did they make you pay for those knives? -No.
你没买下这些刀子吧？ 没有
-Are you sure? -No.
你确定？ 没有
You won't make enough money by selling knives.
卖刀赚不了多少钱的
I just need enough money for the second part of my plan.
我知道 我只需要后续计划的本钱
-What's that? -My Saturn dealership.
后续计划是什么？ 经销废弃物处理设备
Hello.
-Ross. -Emily. Hi.
罗斯 艾蜜莉
How was your flight?
旅途还顺利吗？
It was dreadful.
很惨
It was terrible how I acted when you said those wonderful things.
你对我告白 我的反应却那么差劲
No,that's all right.
没关系
I'm just glad you called.
我很高兴你打来
Ross,there's something that I've got to tell you.
罗斯，我有事要告诉你
There's someone else.
我有男朋友了
Does that mean the same thing in England as it does in America?
这句话在英国的意思 跟在美国一样吗？
She doesn't know who she wants. Me or this "Colin" guy.
她不知道她想要谁 我还是那个柯林
So I told her when she figures it out, give me a call. Maybe I'll still be around.
我叫她想清楚再打给我 也许我还在
When you say "still around," you mean still around like you might be in a relationship...
我问一下，你说也许还在 是你会等她选择你
...or still around like you might have died waiting for the phone to ring?
还是你会等电话等到死？
But it was so right.
原本明明很完美
This isn't how it's supposed to go. There can't be another guy.
现在都乱了， 怎么会有第三者
Of course,there's another guy!
当然有第三者
This is even more perfect.
这样更完美
You have to prove your love!
现在你得证明你的爱
I'm not proving anything. I'm done listening to you.
我什么也不证明 我不会再听你的了
If I hadn't let you talk me into this...
要不是被你说服跑去机场
...I wouldn't have put my fist through the wall.
我也不会搞到去槌墙
You did that?
你槌墙？
I missed and hit the door.
结果没打中打到门
But it opened really hard.
不过门弹得很用力
You have to go to London. You have to go fight for her.
你得去伦敦 什么？ 你得去争取她
That makes sense.
对，有道理
You said you loved her, and she didn't say it back.
你说你爱她，她没有回应
Then she told you about another guy. Go to London. Scare her!
然后她打来说有男朋友 去伦敦吧，她会被吓死
When Rachel was with Paolo, what did you do?
瑞秋跟保罗在一起时 你做了什么？
I made fun of his accent.
我嘲笑他的口音
You sat back and let him have her. You didn't fight.
你让他轻松得手 你完全没争取，没错吧？
I just told you, I made fun of him behind his back.
我说了，我私下取笑他的口音
Oh,I see.
我懂了
-You want that to happen with Emily? -No.
你想让艾蜜莉也被抢走？ 不想
All right then,go fight for her!
好，那就去争取她
It's like a snake pit.
好像一窝蛇喔
That could be you and Emily.
你和艾蜜莉也可以那样
That but nicer.
比他们唯美
Go to London!
飞去伦敦
Really?
真的？
Surprise her. Don't let her go without a fight.
快点，到她家门口， 给她惊喜 别把她拱手让人
All right. I'm going to do it.
好，就这么决定
I'm going to London, and I'll fight for her.
我要去伦敦争取她
Okay. Good luck!
好，加油
Can you pick me up one of those Toblerone bars at the airport?
罗斯，你到了机场 能不能帮我买特大三角巧克力
I did it! I figured out a way to make money.
我想到了！ 我想到赚钱的路子了
I'll open a massage place. Frank will help me.
我要开按摩院，找法兰克帮忙
We'll work it around his schedule, so he doesn't have to quit school.
配合他的时间，他就不必休学
But how can you afford it?
好主意，但你哪来的钱？
We were walking down the street, and we saw your van.
我们走在路上 看见你们办外烩的小巴
-And we realized -I'm telling it!
就想到… 我要说啦
People need transportation, and they need massages to relax.
人们需要交通工具 也需要按摩放松
We can combine the two. I give massages and Frank drives.
我们可以结合两者 我按摩，法兰克开车
I'll bolt a table in the van, and you know what I've got?
我可以在小巴里装个桌子 结果就是什么？
A place that no one will get out of alive?
有进无出的死亡小巴？
Think about it. It's a taxi that people take when they need to relax.
不是，你们想嘛 就是给想放松的人搭的计程车
It's a Relaxi-Taxi!
叫做轻松任你行
The name was my favorite part!
我最想讲的就是名字
-I came up with it. -You did not!
是我想出来的 你乱讲
You came up with Relaxi-Cab. That's not good.
你想的是轻松之行 一点也不好
Oh,my god! Are you in England? Was Emily surprised?
天哪！你在英国吗？ 艾蜜莉惊喜吗？
No,she hasn't come home yet.
不，因为她还没回家
She hasn't been home all night. She must be with the other guy.
她整晚都没回家 显然是跟另一个人在一起
I'm the stupid moron who spent the night here.
我则是在这里守夜的白痴
-What was that? -I just put my fist through another wall.
什么声音？ 我又槌墙了
Tell the guys.
告诉钱德和乔伊
When is the next flight out?
下一班飞机是几点？
About four hours.
大约4小时后
Stay there for a while. If she doesn't show up,come home.
再等一下 如果她还不出现就回来
There's a girl at the restaurant that would be perfect for you.
我刚想到 我们餐厅有个女生很适合你
Tell him about Relaxi-Taxi.
告诉他轻松任你行的事
Ask him if he likes it better than Relaxi-Cab.
问他是不是比轻松之行好
It's not Relaxi-Cab. It's Relaxi-Cab. Like Taxi-Cab.
不是轻松之行，是轻松车行 就像计程车行
That is better.
这个比较好
Do you have any 8's?
你有8吗？
No.
没有
Are we in London?
这里是伦敦吗？
Why are you here? You can't be here.
你怎么在这里？你不能在这里
I've come to talk to Ross.
我有话要对罗斯说
What?
怎么了？
Nothing.
没事
I was going to call him
我本来想打给他…
You came to tell him you love him. I knew it!
你来说你爱他，我就知道
I was right! I'm right,right?
我是对的！我是对的吧？
I'd rather talk to him.
我只想跟他谈
I've been to his apartment and he's not there.
我去过他家，他不在
I need to talk to him. Do you know where he is?
我得跟他谈谈 你们知道他在哪里吗？
Ross,are you there?
罗斯，你在吗？
Ross,I don't know if you hear this, but I'll talk anyway.
我不晓得你听不听得见 不过我就说了
I'm in the States with your sister and friends.
我在美国 跟你的妹妹朋友在一起
It's all over with Colin.
我跟柯林分手了
I came here to tell you that and to tell you
我来告诉你这件事，还有…
Yes,Joey,you can have all the chocolate you want.
乔伊，你想要巧克力就拿吧
I came here to tell you that I love you.
我来告诉你…我爱你
I love you too!
我也爱你
I'll call you right now from the phone booth.
我现在就打公共电话给你
You can't hear me.
你听不见
I wish I knew if you'd heard me.
真想知道你听不听得见
I suppose I've given my neighbors a good laugh.
我不是刚告白完 就是给了邻居笑柄
Mrs. Newman,if you're listening, bugger off. None of your business.
纽曼太太，如果你在听 滚开，不关你的事
There's not much chance you did hear that.
你八成听不见
There's the call waiting...
而且有电话进来了
...so I should go.
我得挂了…
Oh,well.
就这样
Ross,I love you.
罗斯，我爱你
Thank you.
谢谢
I was just at the bank. There was this really hot teller...
我刚才去银行 有个很辣的行员
...and she didn't ask me to do it with her in the vault.
她没有找我去金库嘿咻
Same thing happened to me.
我也是
Pizza delivery girl comes over, gives me the pizza and leaves!
披萨外送小妹来 放下披萨收了钱就走了
No "Nice apartment, bet the bedrooms are huge"?
没说“你家好漂亮” “卧房一定很大吧？”
Nothing!
完全没有
You know what? We have to turn off the porn.
你知道吗？ 我们得把A片关掉
I think you're right.
你说得对
Ready?
准备好了吗？
One,two,three.
一，二，三
That's kind of nice.
蛮好的
That's kind of a relief.
有种解脱感 对
You want to see if we still have it?
想不想看它还在不在？ 想
-Free porn! -We have free porn!
免费A片！ 我们有免费A片！
There's one,two and three.
总共一，二，三
-Oh,my God. -That's so beautiful.
天哪 太美了
-Oh,man. -I can't believe it.
我真不敢相信
I know.
是啊
I like the middle one the best.
我最喜欢中间那个
Don't worry, I won't let the other two know.
放心，我不会告诉另外两个